Milne School; Records ua659
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Milne School Records
1890-2004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua659
32.44 cubic ft. 917 Digital Files
This collection contains materials from the Milne School related to administrative activities from faculty and staff, as well as records pertaining to student activities from various clubs and publications.
Administrative History
The campus laboratory school dates from 1845, when the teacher training primary school was formed. This program was known as the Experimental School until 1867, when it became the Model School of the Albany Normal School. The mission of the experimental school was to provide a convenient location for practice teaching.
In 1890, the State Normal College created a high school teacher practice program which was named the Milne School in 1914, after William J. Milne, the late college president. Dr. Milne had been requested, in 1889, to prepare an overview reorganization plan for the Normal School, and to include a high grade (high school level) professional school. Thus Dr. Milne is considered to be the Father of the high school.
The Milne School was somewhat unique because of its dual purpose as both a high school education program and also as a teacher training environment for college students. The school continued to operate normally for many years, until it came under scrutiny by the state government for who investigated the institution for a lack of diversity in the school. It was discovered that many students were chosen merely because they had other family members who had attended in the past, or were currently enrolled at the Milne School. It was after this investigation that the school began to become more diverse racially.
The school closed its doors in June 1977, after extensive debate on the purpose and merit of the program and because of the economic cut-backs in the State University system in the 1970s. Alumni of the school continued to remain active, with many reunions held, and attended by former student s and faculty. In some instances there have been school-wide reunions attended by all class years.
Scope and Contents
There is very little information on the early years of Milne, partly due to the Willett Street fire of 1905. Most of the earliest records were burned or damaged. Confidential Regents reports date from 1907, and commencement programs date from 1893. Most of the records begin in the late thirties and early forties.
For researchers interested in general background on the Milne School, the history and profile files in the general series may be useful. Information on Milne Hall can be found in files on proposals for a new building in 1949, and within the library frieze and mural plan files dating from 1932. Further information can be found in the University film Library, and by researching the Alumni campus in other Special Collections files.
Data on the student teaching program or the school curriculum can be found in the general reference files under teacher training, student teaching, methods participation, and curriculum. Master Plan 1972 and Methods Participation 1972 include descriptions of Milne's relationship with SUNYA, and justification and objectives for the student teaching program. Also, historic references to the methods program are noted within the committee reports on assessing the effectiveness of teacher training, such as the Teacher Education Committee file of 1958-1969.
There are many reorganization programs within the general files and the closing of Milne series. Note the Five year plan of 1946, and the Future of Milne Committee file of 1952-1967. Another file of interest is the Readjustment of High School Education in 1951.
Reorganization plans and committees peak in the late Sixties and Seventies with several files on the function and role of laboratory schools (C.U.L.S. background dates from 1947). The Fiser report, which evaluates Milne from 1967-1970, the Fretwell recommendations, the N.C.A.T.E. Evaluation of Milne in 1970, and the Three Year Plan of 1972 are useful files. Workshop and symposia files as well as faculty meeting agendas and minutes also present important issues on the present and future of Milne. Follow up studies on students are found in the general file under both class of..., and under follow up studies.
Information on the 1950's lawsuit that forced the integration of the Milne School will not be found within these files. Suits on accident liabilities are in the general files however. Other records of general interest include the scrapbooks which date from 1909, notebooks, yearbooks, newspapers and other student publications.
Acquisition Information
40 cubic feet of administrative records from the Milne School were transferred to the University Archives upon the closing of the school from on June 23 1977. The Collection was originally processed in 1989, but later additional donations of memoribilia from the Milne Alumni and updated practices neccessated a reprocessing in 2016. The order of the series themselvers were altered, but only the subject files and memorobilia were reordered below the series level since 1989.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into fifteen series, separated by subject, and within these series is organized typically alphabetically or chronologically, depending on the discretion of the processor.
Access
Series 6, Confidential Testing and Ranking Files, is restricted due to the presence of student grades. Researchers may access other file series within this collection, yet often files must be reviewed by an archivist to ensure compliance with New York State Public Records laws. An additonal file in Series 5, Closing of Milne, is also restricted. Please consult an archivist for more information.
Albany, New York; Education, Secondary; Student Teaching; Athletics and Sports; Education; Digital Files; UAlbany Academic Administration; Milne School (Albany, N.Y.)
- Annual Reports, 1932-1977; 1; 2.0 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged in chronological order.
  Scope and Contents
  Contains reports arranged chronologically from 1932-1977. The reports for 1941-42 for 1946-47, and 1972-73 are missing. Includes budget requests. Contents of reports include departmental studies, proposals for changes, budget requests for the next school year and overall summaries of the events of the year.
  - Annual Report for 1932-36, 1932-1936 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 1)
  - Annual Report for 1933 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 2)
  - Annual Report for 1937-38, 1938 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 3)
  - Annual Report for 1938-39, 1939 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 4)
  - Annual Report for 1939-40, 1940 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 5)
  - Annual Report for 1940-41, 1941 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 6)
  - Annual Report for 1942-43, 1943 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 7)
  - Annual Report for 1943-44, 1944 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 8)
  - Annual Report for 1944-45, 1945 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 9)
  - Annual Report for 1945-46, 1946 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 10)
  - Annual Report for 1947-48, 1948 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 11)
  - Budget Request for 1947-48, 1948 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 12)
  - Annual Report for 1948-49, 1949 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 13)
  - Annual Report for 1949-50, 1950 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report for 1950-51, 1951 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 15)
  - Budget Request for 1950-51, 1951 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 16)
  - Annual Report for 1951-52, 1952 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 17)
  - Budget Request for 1951-52, 1952 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 18)
  - Annual Report for 1952-53, 1953 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 19)
  - Budget Request for 1952-53, 1953 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1953-54, 1954 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1953-54, 1954 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 22)
  - Budget Request for 1953-55, 1955 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 23)
  - Annual Report for 1954-55, 1955 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 24)
  - Budget Request for 1954-55, 1955 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 25)
  - Annual Report for 1955-56, 1956 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 26)
  - Budget Request for 1955-56, 1956 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1956-57, 1957 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1956-57, 1957 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 29)
  - Budget Request for 1956-57, 1957 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 30)
  - Annual Report for 1957-58, 1958 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 31)
  - Budget Request for 1957-58, 1958 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 32)
  - Annual Report for 1958-59, 1959 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 33)
  - Budget Report for 1958-59, 1959 (Box 1 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 34)
  - Annual Report for 1959-60, 1960 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 1)
  - Budget Request for 1959-60, 1960 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1960-61, 1961 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, Part 2, 1961 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 4)
  - Budget Request for 1960-61, 1961 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 5)
  - Annual Report for 1961-62, 1962 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 6)
  - Annual Report for 1962-63, 1963 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 7)
  - Annual Report for 1963-64, 1964 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1964-65, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1964-65, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 10)
  - Annual Report for 1965-66, 1966 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1966-67, 1967 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1966-67, 1967 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1967-68, 1968 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1967-68, 1968 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1968-69, 1969 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1968-69, 1969 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1969-70, 1970 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1969-70, 1970 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1970-71, 1971 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1970-71, 1971 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, Part 1 for 1971-72, 1972 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, Part 2 for 1971-72, 1972 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 23)
  - Annual Report for 1973-75, 1975 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 24)
  - Annual Report for 1974-75, 1975 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 25)
  - Annual Report for 1975-76, 1976 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 26)
  - Annual Report for 1976-77, 1977 (Box 2 (1-Annual Reports), Folder 27)
- Standing Operations Procedures, 1950-1973; 2; 1.0 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  Faculty lists, calendar, schedules, homeroom sections, admissions, accounts, testing program, textbooks and supplies, booklists, university schedules, handbook, opening of school procedures.
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1950s, ca. 1950-1959 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 1)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1950-51 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 2)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1951-52, 1952 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 3)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1952-53 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 4)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1953-54 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 5)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1954-55 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 6)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1955-56 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 7)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1956-57 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 8)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1957-58 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 9)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1958-59 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 10)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1959-60 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 11)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1960-61 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 12)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1961-62 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 13)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1962-63 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 14)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1963-64 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 15)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1964-65 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 16)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1966-67 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 17)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1967-68 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 18)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1968-69 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 19)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1969-70 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 20)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1970-71 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 21)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1971-72 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 22)
  - Standing Operations Procedures for 1972-73 (Box 3 (2-Standing Operations Procedures), Folder 23)
- Subject Files, 1890-1977; 3; 12.0 cubic ft.
  Arranged Alphabetically.
  This series contains materials related to various administrative functions of the school, the specific teaching departments, to budget reports and meeting minutes.
  - Academic Admissions Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Academic Calendar Memoranda, 1971 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Accreditation, 1960 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Administrative Council Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Administrative Council Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Administrative Council Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Admission, College, Methods of, 1957-1958 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Admissions, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Admissions, 1968 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Admissions, 1971 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Admissions, 1972 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Admissions, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Admissions Background Material, Policy, 1952-1966 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Admissions Criteria - Colleges, 1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Admissions Policy -Campus School, 1962 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Admissions Testing (See Confidential Series), 1968 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Advanced Placement Tests, 1958-1959 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Advisee Day Report, 1971 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Albany High Art Show, 1971 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Alumni, Register Alumni Association, 1893-1940 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Alumni, Roster of Milne Alumni, 1893-1940 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Alumni, Roster of Milne Alumni, 1942-1968 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Alumni, World War II Military Service List, 1945 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Ambassadors (School Service Club), 1952-1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Annual Report Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Art, 1968-1972 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Art Department, 1961-1965 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Assemblies, 1957-1965 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Assemblies, 1969-1971 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Assemblies, 1965-1972 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Assembly, Honors, 1949-1963 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Assembly, Honors, 1957-1959 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Assembly, Honors, 1964-1965 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Assembly, Honors, 1966-1968 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Association of New York State Teachers College Faculties, 1948-1959 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Athletic Clippings, 1960 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Athletic District League, 1960-1965 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Athletics, 1968-1972 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Athletics, 1969-1972 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Athletics, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Athletics, 1971-1972 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Athletics CHVL (Central Hudson Valley League), 1969-1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Athletics CHVL (Central Hudson Valley League), 1970-1971 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Athletics -Section II, 1960s (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Attendance Report, 1962-1963 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Attendance Report, 1963-1964 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Attendance Report, 1964-1965 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Attendance Report, 1965-1966 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Attendance Report, 1966-1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Audio-Visual Equipment, 1966-1972 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Audio Visual Materials, 1960-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Bricks and Ivy - Policy and Memos, 1947-1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Bowler Memorandums, Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Bowler Memorandums, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Bowler Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Bright Child, 1956-1958 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Budget Equipment, 1968-1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Budget Expenditures, 1962-1963 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Budget Expenditures, 1965-1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Budget Expenditures, 1968-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Budget Expenditures, 1970-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Budget Expenditures, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Budget Requests, 1955-1956 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Budget Requests, 1961-1962 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Budget Requests, 1968-1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Budget Requests and Expenditures, 1960-1961 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Budget-Students-Plays, 1932-1935 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Building Equipment and Safety, 1970-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Building -New, 1956-1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Building Plans, 1947-1948; 1955-1956 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Building Plans, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Business Education Department, 1965-1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Business Education Department, 1968-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Calendars, 1930s; ca. 1960 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Calendars, 1969-1972 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Capital District League Scheduling, 1960s (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Card Party, 1950s; ca. 1960 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Card Party, 1967-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Catalog and Classification-19Library, 1960s (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Certification, 1959-1963 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Chaperone Assignments, 1963-1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Christmas Plays, 1933 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Christmas Programs, 1946-1958 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Christmas Programs, 1949-1965 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Civil Defense Activities, 1960-1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Class Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Class Activities, 1970-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Class Activities, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Class Photograph, 1937; ca. 1963 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Class Roster, 1947-1948 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Class Roster, 1948-1949 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Codes, Dress and Behavior, 1968-1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, 1971 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Preparation, 1956; 1958; 1960-1961; 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Preparation, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Commencement-Preparation, 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Commencement-Preparation, 1971 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Commencement-Preparation, 1972 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Commencement Programs, 1894; 1898-1999; 1908; 1913-1914; 1917-1926 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Commencement Programs, 1929; 1931-1932; 1934-1937; 1939-1942 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Commencement Programs, 1943-1953 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Commencement Programs, 1958-1965; 1967-1973; 1977 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Committee on the Improvement of College Teaching, 1950 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Committee on Professional Semester, 1955-1956 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Committee on Use of Lab Schools (CULS), 1970-1971 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Committee Reports, 1936-1938 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Committee Reports: Progress Reports to Parents, 1936-1940 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Computer Room, 1965-1968 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Course Outlines, 1968 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Crimson and White Expenses, 1931-1934 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Crimson and White, Policy and Memos, 1942-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Curriculum, 1954-1961 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Curriculum, 1966-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Curriculum, 1969-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Curriculum, 1971-1972 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Curriculum Readings - English 12, 1971-1972 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Curriculum Statements, 1966 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Daily Bulletins, 1965-1966 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Daily Bulletins, 1967-1968 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Daily Schedule, 1943-1944 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Dances, 1969-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Demonstration-Observation Program, 1938-1966 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Demonstration-Observation Program, 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Departmental Files, Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Departmental Head Memos, 1951-1952 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Departmental Planning Committee, 1944-1947 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Development-Guidance Office -Annual Report, 1935-1941 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Driver Education Program, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Driver Education Program, 1967-1972 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)